Since the program is project-based,
因为这个项目是基于项目的
we're going to dive into your first project.
我们将进入你的第一个项目
Now you're probably thinking,
现在你可能在想
you guys haven't even taught me anything yet.
你们还没教过我什么
Well, you can think of this first project as a warm up.
好吧 你可以把这个项目当成一个温暖的项目
It will help you become comfortable with the project submission and review process,
它将帮助您熟悉项目提交和复审流程
as well as introduce you to a few of
向你介绍几个
the concepts you'll be learning throughout the rest of the program.
你会在整个计划中学习的概念
After you finish and submit your projects,
完成并提交项目后
it will go to one of our expert reviewers.
就会去参加我们的专家评审
For most projects, if there's something that needs improvement,
对于大多数项目 如果有需要改进的东西
you'll get feedback on how to improve it,
你会得到关于如何改进的反馈
and you can resubmit as many times as you need to in order to pass the project.
您可以按需要多次重新提交以传递项目
Since this project is a warm up,
因为这个项目是一个温暖的项目
you'll just submit it once, get feedback,
你只要提交一次反馈就好了
and then move on to the next project regardless of how you did.
然后继续下一个项目不管你是怎么做的
So don't worry at all.
所以别担心
You can't fail. Just try your best.
你不能失败 尽力吧
Ready to get started?
准备好开始了吗
Take a look at the next session for the description of the project. Good luck.这意味着我会在这里和那里弹出来为您正在学习的内容提供更多背景信息。
最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6